John H. Cornehlsen Papers 5730
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series I: Psychological Profiles
  - Sub-Series A: Profiles done for Companies
    - Company C: Be, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 22)
      Code:78D
    - Company C: Bi, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 23)
      Code:79B
    - Company C: Bi, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Company C: Bo, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 25)
      Code:80B
    - Company C: Bu, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 26)
      Code:81B
    - Company C: Ch, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Company C: Ci, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 28)
      Code:47C
    - Company C: Co, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 29)
      Code:48C
    - Company C: Cr, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Company C: Da, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 31)
      Code:44D
    - Company C: De, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 32)
      Code:45D
    - Company C: Di, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 33)
      Code:46D
    - Company C: Du, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Company C: Ec, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 35)
      Code:16E
    - Company C: El, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - Company C: Fe, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 37)
      Code:30F
    - Company C: Fe, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 1)
      Code:28F
    - Company C: Fi, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Company C: Fu, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 3)
      Code:29F
    - Company C: Ga, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 4)
      Code:27G
    - Company C: Ge, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 5)
      Code:28G
    - Company C: Gi, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Company C: Ha, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 7)
      Code:61H
    - Company C: Ha, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 8)
      Code:62H
    - Company C: He, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Company C: He, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 10)
      Code:64H
    - Company C: He, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 11)
      Code:65H
    - Company C: Ho, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 12)
      Code:56H
    - Company C: Ho, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 13)
      Code:57H
    - Company C: Ho, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 14)
      Code:58H
    - Company C: Ho, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 15)
      Code:59H
    - Company C: Hu, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 16)
      Code:60H
    - Company C: Is, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Company C: Ja, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 18)
      Code:14J
    - Company C: Ke, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 19)
      Code:37K
    - Company C: Ke, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Company C: Ko, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 21)
      Code:35K
    - Company C: Kr, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 22)
      Code:36K
    - Company C: La, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 23)
      Code:46L
    - Company C: La, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 24)
      Code:44L
    - Company C: Le, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Company C: Lo, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 26)
      Code:45L
    - Company C: Ma, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 27)
      Code:83M
    - Company C: Ma, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 28)
      Code:84M
    - Company C: Ma, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Company C: Me, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 30)
      Code:86M
    - Company C: Me, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 1)
      Code:85M
    - Company C: Mi, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 2)
      Code:87M
    - Company C: Mo, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Company C: Mo, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Company C: Mu, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 5)
      Code:88M
    - Company C: Na, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Company C: Ne, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 7)
      Code:18N
    - Company C: Ne, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 8)
      Code:19N
    - Company C: No, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 9)
      Code:20N
    - Company C: No, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 10)
      Code:21N
    - Company C: Ol, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Company C: Pe, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Company C: Pe, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Company C: Pe, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 14)
      Code:26P
    - Company C: Ph, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Company C: Po, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 16)
      Code:27P
    - Company C: Ro, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Company C: Sa, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 18)
      Code:76S
    - Company C: Sm, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 19)
      Code:71S
    - Company C: Sm, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 20)
      Code:72S
    - Company C: Sm, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 21)
      Code:74S
    - Company C: So, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 22)
      Code:73S
    - Company C: Sw, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Company C: Ti, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 24)
      Code:35T
    - Company C: Th, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 25)
      Code:33T
    - Company C: Th, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 26)
      Code:34T
    - Company C: Th, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Company C: Va, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Company C: Wa, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Company C: Wh, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 30)
      Code:36W
    - Company C: Wo, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 31)
      Code:40W
    - Company C: Zi, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 32)
      Code:3Z
    - Company D: Be, 1958 (Box 25, Folder 1)
      Code:88B
    - Company D: Ba, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 2)
      Code:89B
    - Company D: Bo, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Company D: Ca, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 4)
      Code:55C
    - Company D: Ca, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Company D: Co, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 6)
      Code:56C
    - Company D: Da, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 7)
      Code:52D
    - Company D: Di, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 8)
      Code:51D
    - Company D: Gi, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Company D: Go, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Company D: Ha, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Company D: Ha, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 12)
      Code: 73H
    - Company D: Ha, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Company D: Ho, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Company D: Ho, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 15)
      Code:74H
    - Company D: Jo, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Company D: Ka, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Company D: Ki, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 18)
      Code:38K
    - Company D: Ki, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 19)
      Code:39K
    - Company D: Kl, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 20)
      Code:40K
    - Company D: Kr, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 21)
      Code:41K
    - Company D: La, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 22)
      Code:51L
    - Company D: Le, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 23)
      Code:48L
    - Company D: Le, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 24)
      Code:49L
    - Company D: Lo, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 25)
      Code:50L
    - Company D: Ma, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 26)
      Code:94M
    - Company D: Ma, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Company D: Ma, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - Company D: Ma, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - Company D: Me, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 30)
      Code:95M
    - Company D: Mi, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 31)
      Code:96M
    - Company D: Pa, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - Company D: Ph, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 34)
      Code:29P
    - Company D: Pr, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 35)
    - Company D: Ro, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 36)
      Code:43R
    - Company D: Ro, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 37)
    - Company D: Sa, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 38)
    - Company D: Sc, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 39)
    - Company D: Si, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 1)
      Code:81S
    - Company D: Sw, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 2)
      Code:82S
    - Company D: Ta, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Company D: Th, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 4)
      Code:36T
    - Company D: Wa, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 5)
      Code:48W
    - Company D: X, 1958 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Company D: Ya, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Company D: Zi, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Company E: Ad, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Company E: Al, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 10)
      Code:36A
    - Company E: Al, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Company E: An, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Company E: Be, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Company E: Be, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 14)
      Code:91B
    - Company E: Be, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Company E: Bl, 1958 (Box 26, Folder 16)
      Code: 90B
    - Company E: Bo, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Company E: Bo, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Company E: Co, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 19)
      Code:57C
    - Company E: Co, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Company E: Do, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Company E: Do, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 22)
      Code:53D
    - Company E: Ed, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Company E: Ev, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 24)
      Code:18E
    - Company E: Ga, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Company E: Gu, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 26)
      Code:31G
    - Company E: Ha, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - Company E: Ha, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - Company E: Ho, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - Company E: Hu, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 30)
      Code:75H
    - Company E: Jo, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - Company E: Ke, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - Company E: Ku, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 33)
      Code:44R
    - Company E: Ly, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 34)
      Code:52L
    - Company E: Ma, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 35)
    - Company E: Me, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 36)
      Code:97M
    - Company E: Mo, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 37)
    - Company E: Mu, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 38)
    - Company E: Na, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 39)
    - Company E: Ne, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 40)
      Code:72N
    - Company E: Pa, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 41)
      Code:30P
    - Company E: Pe, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 42)
    - Company E: Pi, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Company E: Re, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Company E: Ro, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 3)
      Code:45R
    - Company E: Sc, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Company E: Sc, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 5)
      Code:83S
    - Company E: Si, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 6)
      Code:84S
    - Company E: Sm, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Company E: Sm, 1958 (Box 27, Folder 8)
      Code:85S
    - Company E: St, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Company E: Tu, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Company E: Tu, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 11)
      Code:37T
    - Company E: We, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Company E: Wi, 1958 (Box 27, Folder 13)
      Code:49W
    - Company F: Gr, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Company G: Ha, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Company G: Ro, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Company G: We, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Company H: Co, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Company I: Co, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Company I: Mo, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Company J: Ba, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Company K: Pe, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Company L: So, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Company M: No, 1958 (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Company N: Ja, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Company O: Ro, 1956 (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Company P: Gi, 1956 (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - Company Q: Jo, 1955 (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - Company R: Mc, 1957 (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - Company S: Co, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - Company T: Ba, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - Company T: Bi, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 32)
    - Company T: Bi, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 33)
    - Company T: Ha, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 34)
    - Company T: Miscellaneous, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 35)
    - Company T: Sh, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 36)
    - Company T: To, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 37)
    - Company T: Pa, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 38)
    - Company U: Al, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 39)
    - Company U: Am, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Company U: Br, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Company U: Bu, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Company U: Ca, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Company U: Co, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Company U: Di, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Company U: Em, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Company U: En, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Company U: Fa, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Company U: Fo, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Company U: Go, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Company U: Go, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Company U: Ha, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Company U: Ha, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Company U: He, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Company U: He, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Company U: Jo, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Company U: Jo, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Company U: Ke, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Company U: Kl, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Company U: Ku, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Company U: Mi, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Company U: Ro, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Company U: Ro, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Company U: Sa, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Company U: Sc, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Company U: Sm, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - Company U: Sp, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - Comapny V: Br, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - Comapny V: Br, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - Comapny V: Sk, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 31)
    - Comapny V: Sk, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 32)
    - Comapny V: To, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 33)
    - Company W: Bu, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 34)
      Code:82B
    - Company X: We, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 35)
    - Company Y: Ha, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 36)
      Code: 67H
    - Cmpany Z: WA, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 1)
      Code:41W
    - Company AA: Me, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 2)
      Code:90M
    - Company AB: Ha, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Company AC: Fa, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Company AD: Ga, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Company AE: Ga, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Company AE: Ad, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Company AE: Gi, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Company AE: Ka, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Company AE: Mi, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Company AE: Ri, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Company AE: Sa, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Company AE: Ul, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Company AE: Wh, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Company AE: Wo, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Company AF: An, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Company AF: Ar, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Company AF: Au, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Company AF: Ba, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Company AF: Be, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Company AF: Bi, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Company AF: Br, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Company AF: Br, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Company AF: Br, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - Company AF: Br, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - Company AF: Br, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - Company AF: Ca, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - Company AF: Ch, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - Company AF: Ch, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - Company AF: Co, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 30)
    - Company AF: Co, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 31)
    - Company AF: Co, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 32)
    - Company AF: Co, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 33)
    - Company AF: Co, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 34)
    - Company AF: Cr, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 35)
    - Company AF: Cr, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 36)
    - Company AF: de, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 37)
    - Company AF: De, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 38)
    - Company AF: Do, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 39)
    - Company AF: En, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 40)
    - Company AF: Fe, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 41)
    - Company AF: Fi, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 42)
    - Company AF: Fr, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 43)
    - Company AF: Ga, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 44)
    - Company AF: Ga, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 45)
    - Company AF: Ga, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 46)
    - Company AF: Ga, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 47)
    - Company AF: Ga, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 48)
    - Company AF: Go, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 49)
    - Company AF: Go, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 50)
    - Company AF: Ha, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 51)
    - Company AF: Ha, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 52)
    - Company AF: He, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 53)
    - Company AF: He, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 54)
    - Company AF: He, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 55)
    - Company AF: Hi, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 56)
    - Company AF: Ho, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 57)
    - Company AF: Ja, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 58)
    - Company AF: Ja, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 59)
    - Company AF: Ja, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 60)
    - Company AF: Je, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 61)
    - Company AF: Jo, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 62)
    - Company AF: Jo, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 63)
    - Company AF: Jo, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 64)
    - Company AF: Ke, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 65)
    - Company AF: Kl, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 66)
    - Company AF: Ko, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 67)
    - Company AF: La, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Company AF: Le, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Company AF: Le, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Company AF: Le, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Company AF: Le, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Company AF: Lu, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Company AF: Ly, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Company AF: Ma, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Company AF: Ma, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Company AF: Ma, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Company AF: Mc, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Company AF: Mc, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Company AF: Mi, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Company AF: Wa, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Company AF: Mi, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Company AF: Mo, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Company AF: Mo, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Company AF: Mu, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Company AF: Ne, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Company AF: Ne, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Company AF: Pe, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - Company AF: Pi, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - Company AF: Pi, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - Company AF: Po, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - Company AF: Re, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - Company AF: Ri, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - Company AF: Ro, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 27)
    - Company AF: Sc, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 28)
    - Company AF: Sc, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 29)
    - Company AF: Sc, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 30)
    - Company AF: Sc, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 31)
    - Company AF: Se, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 32)
    - Company AF: Jo, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 33)
    - Company AF: Sh, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 34)
    - Company AF: Sm, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 35)
    - Company AF: Sm, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 36)
    - Company AF: So, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 37)
    - Company AF: St, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 38)
    - Company AF: St, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 39)
    - Company AF: St, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 40)
    - Company AF: Ta, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 41)
    - Company AF: Ta, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 42)
    - Company AF: Ts, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 43)
    - Company AF: Um, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 44)
    - Company AF: Wa, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 45)
    - Company AF: Wa, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 46)
    - Company AF: We, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 47)
    - Company AF: Wi, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 48)
    - Company AF: Wu, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 49)
    - Company AF: Za, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 50)
    - Company AF: Za, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 51)
    - Company AF: Ze, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 52)
    - Company AF: Zi, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 53)
    - Company AF: Zu, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 54)
    - Company AF: Reports, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 55)
    - Company AG: Sa, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 56)
    - Company AH: Bu, 1948 (Box 30, Folder 57)
    - Company AH: Br, 1948 (Box 30, Folder 58)
    - Company AH: Fr, 1948 (Box 30, Folder 59)
    - Company AH: Fr, 1948 (Box 30, Folder 60)
    - Company AH: Ga, 1948 (Box 30, Folder 61)
    - Company AH: Gr, 1948 (Box 30, Folder 62)
    - Company AH: Pa, 1948 (Box 30, Folder 63)
    - Company AH: Ra, 1948 (Box 30, Folder 64)
    - Company AH: Sh, 1948 (Box 30, Folder 65)
    - Company AH: Sk, 1948 (Box 30, Folder 66)
    - Company AH: Wi, 1948 (Box 30, Folder 67)
    - Company AI: Le, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 68)
    - Company AI: Me, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 69)
    - Company AJ: Sc, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 70)
    - Company AK: We, 1959 (Box 30, Folder 71)
    - Company AL: Ca, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 72)
    - Company AL: Fi, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 73)
    - Company AM: Ko, 1963 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Company AN: To, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Company AO: An, 1958 (Box 31, Folder 3)
      Code: 34A
    - Company AO: Br, 1959 (Box 31, Folder 4)
      Code: 86B
    - Company AO: Bu, 1957 (Box 31, Folder 5)
      Code: 87B
    - Company AO: Co, 1957 (Box 31, Folder 6)
      Code: 51C
    - Company AO: Co, 1957 (Box 31, Folder 7)
      Code: 52C
    - Company AO: Cu, 1957 (Box 31, Folder 8)
      Code: 53C
    - Company AO: Da, 1957 (Box 31, Folder 9)
      Code: 50D
    - Company AO: Da, 1957 (Box 31, Folder 10)
      Code: 48D
    - Company AO: Du, 1957 (Box 31, Folder 11)
      Code: 49d
    - Company AO: Fi, 1957 (Box 31, Folder 12)
      Code: 31F
    - Company AO: Fo, 1957 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Company AO: Fu, 1957 (Box 31, Folder 14)
      Code: 32F
    - Company AO: He, 1957 (Box 31, Folder 15)
      Code: 71H
    - Company AO: He, 1957 (Box 31, Folder 16)
      Code: 70H
    - Company AO: Hu, 1957 (Box 31, Folder 17)
      Code: 72H
    - Company AO: Ja, 1957 (Box 31, Folder 18)
      Code: 16J
    - Company AO: Mo, 1957 (Box 31, Folder 19)
      Code: 93M
    - Company AO: Ph, 1957 (Box 31, Folder 20)
      Code: 28P
    - Company AO: Ri, 1957 (Box 31, Folder 21)
      Code: 41R
    - Company AO: Ro, 1957 (Box 31, Folder 22)
      Code: 42R
    - Company AO: Se, 1957 (Box 31, Folder 23)
      Code: 80S
    - Company AO: Sn, 1957 (Box 31, Folder 24)
      Code: 79S
    - Company AO: Mu, 1957 (Box 31, Folder 25)
      Code: 92M
    - Company AO: Wh, 1957 (Box 31, Folder 26)
      Code: 47W
    - Company AO: Wi, 1957 (Box 31, Folder 27)
      Code: 44W
    - Company AO: Wo, 1957 (Box 31, Folder 28)
      Code: 45W
    - Company AO: Wu, 1957 (Box 31, Folder 29)
      Code: 46W
    - Company AP: Cl, 1957 (Box 31, Folder 30)
    - Company AP: Ni, 1957 (Box 31, Folder 31)
    - Company AP: Sa, 1957 (Box 31, Folder 32)
    - Company AP: We, 1957 (Box 31, Folder 33)
    - Company AQ: Ad, 1957 (Box 31, Folder 34)
    - Company AR: Ni, 1956 (Box 31, Folder 35)
    - Company AS: Wa, 1970 (Box 31, Folder 36)
    - Company AT: Yo, 1948 (Box 31, Folder 37)
    - Company AU, Inc.: He, 1959 (Box 31, Folder 38)
      Code: 69H
    - Company AV: Ni, 1955 (Box 31, Folder 39)
    - Company AW: Co, 1955 (Box 31, Folder 40)
    - Company AX: Ad, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 41)
    - Company AX: De, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 42)
    - Company AX: Pe, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 43)
    - Company AX: Ra, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 44)
    - Company AY: Gu, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 45)
    - Company AZ: Mi, 1957 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Company BA: Bu, 1955 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Company BB: OB, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Company BC: Ad, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Company BC: Ar, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Company BC: De, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Company BC: Go, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Company BC: Ol, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Company BD: Mo, 1970 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Company BE: To, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Company BF: Cr, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Company BG: Wi, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Company BH: Ke, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Company BI: Mo, 1960 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Company BJ: Po, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Company BK: Wi, 1960 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Company BL: Ku, 1948 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Company BM: Pa, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Company BN: Ha, 1961 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Company BO: Ri, 1961 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Company BP: Ma, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Company BQ: Gr, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Company BR: Co, 1967 (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - Company BR: Di, 1967 (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - Company BR: Fa, 1967 (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - Company BR: Ha, 1967 (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - Company BR: He, 1967 (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - Company BR: He, 1967 (Box 32, Folder 28)
    - Company BR: Mo, 1967 (Box 32, Folder 29)
    - Company BR: Mc, 1967 (Box 32, Folder 30)
    - Company BR: So, 1967 (Box 32, Folder 31)
    - Company BR: Wa, 1967 (Box 32, Folder 32)
    - Company BS: Wi, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 33)
    - Company BT: La, 1967 (Box 32, Folder 34)
    - Company BU: Gl, 1959 (Box 32, Folder 35)
      Code: 17E
    - Company BV: Da, 1967 (Box 32, Folder 36)
      Code: 47D
    - Company BW: Du, 1957 (Box 32, Folder 37)
    - Company BX: Pe, 1957 (Box 32, Folder 38)
    - Company BY: Ne, 1961 (Box 32, Folder 39)
    - Company BZ: Ru, 1958 (Box 32, Folder 40)
      Code: 37R
    - Company CA: Cr, 1961 (Box 32, Folder 41)
    - Company CA: Cr, 1961 (Box 32, Folder 42)
    - Company CB Cases: Ad, 1970 (Box 32, Folder 43)
    - Company CB Cases: Al, 1959 (Box 32, Folder 44)
      Code: 35A
    - Company CB Cases: Al, 1967 (Box 32, Folder 45)
    - Company CB Cases: Al, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Company CB Cases: Al, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Company CB Cases: An, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Company CB Cases: An, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Company CB Cases: Ar, 1964 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Company CB Cases: Ba, 1972 (Box 33, Folder 6)